Mitchell Zilberg

Web and multimedia developer who excels in a team environment and under the pressure of strict deadlines. A former broadcast media and multimedia specialist who plans to incorporate my project-based work experience into the tech industry.

Education

CareerFoundry, Online — Full-Stack Web Development
October 2020 - PRESENT

Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON — *Television-Broadcasting*April 2020

John Abbott College, Montreal, QC — *Media Arts & Literature*December 2017

Projects

Pokedex: Front-end Javascript application

Communicates with an external API to display a list of pokemon.

MyFlix App: Full-stack React & Node application

Displays a list of movies, allows users to register and personalize their own list of favourite movies by communicating with a DIY API.

Chat App: React Native mobile application

Lets users enter a chat room to communicate with their friends.

Work Experience

School Photographer- Lifetouch Canada, ON & QC

October 2020 - Present

Set up and wrap equipment, photograph up to 200 kids per day.

Supervisor, Show Producer, Box Office, & Bartender- Absolute

Comedy, Ottawa, ON

March 2017 - January 2020

Hired, trained, made weekly schedules for, and supervised doormen. Booked reservations over the phone (Microsoft Excel), handled complaints, and checked-in customers while working the box office.

Grip & Camera Operator- MATV, Gatineau, QC

June 2019 - January 2020

Set up, wrapped, and operated industry standard television camera & audio equipment.

Director, Shooter, & Editor-TVC Basse-Lievre, Gatineau, QC

June 2019 - September 2019

Directed, shot, and edited a four-part series on community events that took place during the summer of 2019 in the Basse-Lievre region.

Ottawa, Ontario (613) 618-2496 mzilbergdeveloper@gmail.com

Linkedin, Github, & Portfolio

https://bit.ly/39Hu7rc

https://github.com/mitche |lzilberg

https://mitchellzilberg.gith ub.io/portfolio-website/

Tools (* = some experience)

HTML

CSS. SCSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript ES6

DOM manipulation

jQuery

Git, Github & Version Control

Ajax

React.js

Redux

React Native

Node.js

Express.js

NPM

RESTful Api's

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

Angular*

TypeScript*

AWS*

Adobe Premiere

Davinci Resolve

Microsoft Word / Excel

Adobe After Effects*

Adobe Audition*

Photoshop*

Skills

Bilingual in French & English.

Test driven development approach.

Experienced with a project-based work load.

Mitchell Zilberg

Développeur web et multimédia qui excelle dans un environnement de travail d'équipe et sous la pression de délais stricts. Avec de l'expérience en médias audiovisuels et multimédia, je prévois d'intégrer celle-ci dans des projets de l'industrie technologique.

Éducation

CareerFoundry- en ligne - *Développement Web Full-Stack* octobre 2020 - présent

Collège Algonquin- Ottawa, ON - Télédiffusion

Gradué avec DESO en avril 2020

Collège John Abbott- Montréal, QC - Art des médias et littérature Gradué avec DEC en décembre 2017

Projets

Pokedex: JavaScript

Communique avec un API externe pour afficher une liste de Pokémon.

MyFlix App: Application React & Node

Affiche une liste de films, permet aux utilisateurs de s'inscrire et de personnaliser leur propre liste de films préférés.

Chat App: Application mobile React Native

Permet aux utilisateurs de communiquer avec leurs amis.

Expériences de travail

Photograph scolaire - Lifetouch Canada, ON & QC

octobre 2020 - présent

Préparer et installer l'équipement, photographier jusqu'à 200 enfants par jour.

Superviseur, producteur de spectacle, guichet de location, et barman- Absolute Comedy, Ottawa, ON

mars 2017 - janvier 2020

En charge des embauches, former de nouveaux employés, établir des horaires hebdomadaires et superviser les portiers. En charge de prendre des réservations par téléphone, traiter les plaintes, et enregistré les clients en travaillant au guichet. Utilisation de Microsoft Excel.

Opérateur de prise et de caméra- MATV, Gatineau, QC

juin 2019 - janvier 2020

Configurer, préparer et utiliser une caméra de télévision standard et équipement audio.

Réalisateur et monteur- TVC Basse-Lièvre, Gatineau, QC

juin 2019 - septembre 2019

Réalisation, tournage et montage d'une série en quatre parties, sur les événements communautaires qui ont eu lieu au cours de l'été 2019 dans la région de Basse-Lièvre.

Ottawa, Ontario
(613) 618-2496
mzilbergdeveloper@gmail.com

Linkedin, Github & Portfolio

https://bit.lv/39Hu7rc

https://github.com/mitche llzilberg

https://mitchellzilberg.github.io/portfolio-website/

Technologies

(* = certaines expériences)

HTML

CSS, SCSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript ES6

DOM manipulation

jQuery

Git, Github & Version Control

Ajax

React.js

Redux

React Native

Node.js

Express.js

NPM

RESTful Api's

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

Angular*

TypeScript*

AWS*

Adobe Premiere

Davinci Resolve

Microsoft Word / Excel

Adobe After Effects*

Adobe Audition*

Photoshop*

Compétences

Bilingue en français et anglais, à l'orale et à l'écrit

Expérience avec la charge de travail basée sur les projets